var questions=[{"question":"When was the film released?",
               "option1":"1994",
               "option2":"1982",
               "option3":"1997",
               "option4":"2001",
               "answer":"1"
               },{
               "question":"What type of animal is Rafiki?",
               "option1":"Baboon",
               "option2":"Mandrill",
               "option3":"Tamarin",
               "option4":"Spider Monkey",
               "answer":"2"
               },{
               "question":"What is Simba's mother's name?",
               "option1":"Sarabi",
               "option2":"Uru",
               "option3":"Zuza",
               "option4":"Shenzi",
               "answer":"1"
               },{
               "question":"What is Scar doing when he first appears in the movie?",
               "option1":"Talking to Mufasa",
               "option2":"Attending Simba's presentation ceremony",
               "option3":"Playing with a mouse before he eats it",
               "option4":"Plotting with the hyenas",
               "answer":"3"
               },{
               "question":"What animals do Simba and Nala ride in 'I Just Can't Wait to Be King'?",
               "option1":"Zebras",
               "option2":"Rhinos",
               "option3":"Elephants",
               "option4":"Ostriches",
               "answer":"4"
               },{
               "question":"What is Nala's mother's name?",
               "option1":"Savanna",
               "option2":"Sarafina",
               "option3":"Zira",
               "option4":"Kiara",
               "answer":"2"
               },{
               "question":"What area is Simba specifically forbidden from going to?",
               "option1":"The Watering Hole",
               "option2":"The Cheetah Hunting Ground",
               "option3":"The Elephant Graveyard",
               "option4":"Rafiki's Tree",
               "answer":"3"
               },{
               "question":"What are Mufasa's last words?",
               "option1":"'Run, Simba! Run!'",
               "option2":"'You must!'",
               "option3":"'Scar, Brother, help me!'",
               "option4":"'Avenge me, my son.'",
               "answer":"3"
               },{
               "question":"What does Hakuna Matata mean?",
               "option1":"Return home",
               "option2":"Family first",
               "option3":"No worries",
               "option4":"Just relax",
               "answer":"3"
               },{
               "question":"Which character speaks to Simba right before he becomes king?",
               "option1":"Nobody",
               "option2":"Rafiki",
               "option3":"Nala",
               "option4":"Zazu",
               "answer":"2"
               },{
               "question":"Who is the last new character introduced in the film?",
               "option1":"Simba and Nala's daughter",
               "option2":"SImba's brother",
               "option3":"Nala's brother",
               "option4":"Simba and Nala's son",
               "answer":"1"
               }];